Guide to the Jennings Wood collection of Confederate imprints, 1862-1865 MS2127
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 439)
  (House bill, no 123.) A bill to be entitled An act making appropriations for the support of the government of the Confederate States of America from July 1 to December 31, 1864, and to supply a deficiency. 12 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 440)
  (House bill, no 124.) A bill to be entitled An act making appropriations for the postal service of the Confederate States, for the year 1862 and 1863. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 441)
  (House of Representatives.) Joint resolutions requiring the settlement of the accounts of the Post-Off ice Department prior to the first day of July, 1863. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 442)
  Preamble and resolutions suggesting the removal of the present Secretary of the Treasury. 2 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 443)
  Resolutions declaring the supremacy of the civil over the military law. 2 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 444)
  (House bill no. 135.) A bill to be entitled An act to provide for the settlement of claims against the Confederate States, for property lost, captured or destroyed, while in the military service of the Confederate States, or which has been taken or impressed for their use. 4 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 453)
  (House bill, no. 191.) A bill to be entitled "An act to facilitate the settlement of claims of deceased officers and soldiers." 4 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 454)
  (House bill, no. 203.) A bill to be entitled "An act to protect the Confederate States against frauds and to provide remedies against officers and employees of the government committing them." 8 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 458)
  (House bill, no. 230.) A bill to be entitled "An act to amend An act to provide revenue from commodities imported from foreign countries," approved May 21st, 1864. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 459)
  (House bill, no. 231.)A bill to be entitled "An act to exempt from taxation loans made on hypothecation of non-taxable bonds. 1 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 460)
  (House bill, no. 232.) A bill to be entitled "An act to exempt from taxation the capital of bonds and certificates issued by the Confederate States." 1 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 461)
  (House bill, no. 233.) A bill to be entitled An act to consolidate and amend the laws relative to impressments. 8 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 462)
  (House bill, no. 239.) A bill to be entitled An act to organize the Supreme Court. 4 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 463)
  (House bill, no. 240-Secret session.) A bill to provide for the establishment of a Bureau of Special and Secret Service. 8 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 467)
  (House bill, no. 267. -Secret.)A bill to suspend the privilege of writ of habeas corpus, in certain cases, for a limited time. 6 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 469)
  (House of Representatives.) Amendment to the bill to provide more effectually for the reduction and redemption of the currency. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 471)
  (House bill no. 274.) A bill to increase the pay of marines to that received by the infantry of the army. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 472)
  (House bill no. 275.) A bill to authorize the employment of instructors for the acting midshipment of the navy, and to regulate their rank and pay. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 473)
  (House bill no. 276.) A bill making an appropriation to erect additional quarters for acting midshipment at Drewry's Bluff. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 474)
  (House of Representatives, no. 277.) A bill making an appropriation for the removal of the naval rope walk and erection of the same. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 475)
  (House of Representatives, no. 278.) A bill to increase the number of acting midshipment in the navy, and to prescribe the manner of appointment. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 476)
  (House of Representatives, no. 279.) A bill to provide for the transfer of certain mechanics, artizans and other persons, from the army to the navy. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 477)
  (House of Representatives, no. 280.) A bill to be entitled "An act to impose a duty on tobacco and an additional duty on cotton exported from the Confederate States." 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 478)
  (House of Representatives.) Amendment to the bill to provide more effectually for the reduction and redemption of the currency. [Richmond 1864.] 2 p. 25 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 479)
  (House of Representatives.) Substitute for the bill (H.R. 229) to provide more effectually for the reduction and redemption of the currency. 4 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 481)
  (House of Representatives.)A resolution upon the subject of peace. 2 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 482)
  (House of Representatives.) Resolution relating to the war and negotiations for peace. 2 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 483)
  (House of Representatives.) Amendment to bill to authorize the consolidation of companies, battalions and regiments. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 484)
  (House of Representatives.) Amendment to the bill to be entitled "An act to authorize the consolidation of companies, battalions and regiments." 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 485)
  (House of Representatives.) A resolution [relating to overtures of peace.1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 486)
  (House of Representatives.) A bill to be entitled An act more effectually to provide for the reduction and redemption of the currency. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 487)
  (House of Representatives, no. 285.) A bill to be entitled An act to lay a tax for revenue to provide for the common defence and carrying on of the government of the Confederate States. 6 p. 22 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 488)
  (House of Representatives, no. 286.) A bill to be entitled An act to levy and collect taxes for the common defence and for the support of the government for the year 1865, and to repeal certain tax laws. 6 p. 22 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 489)
  (House of Representatives, no. 287.) A bill to be entitled An act to authorize the 2d auditor of the Treasury, or a commissioner, to be appointed by the Secretary of the Treasury with the consent of the President, to take proof as to the expenditures of the State of Tennessee, in constructing military defences and the support of her army previous to its transfer to the Confederate government. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 490)
  A bill to be entitled An act to provide for organizing, arming and disciplining the militia of the Confederate States, and for governing such part of them as may be employed in the service of the Confederate States, and for calling them forth to execute the laws of the Confederate States, suppress insurrections and repel invasions. [Richmond, 1864.] 14 p.23 l/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 493)
  (House bill no. 303.) A bill to be entitled An act for the further organization of the field artillery of the Confederate States. 2 p. 25 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 494)
  (House of Representatives, no. 307.) A bill to be entitled An act authorizing the Secretary of the Treasury to borrow specie, to be applied to the redemption and reduction of the currency. 4 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 495)
  Amendments to the bill to be entitled An act to authorize the consolidation of companies, battalions and regiments. 3 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 496)
  (House bill no. 311.) A bill to provide additional clothing and privileges to troops in the field. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 497)
  (House of Representatives.) .. Substitute for the bill ( H. R. 203) to protect the Confederate States against frauds, and to provide remedies against officers and employees of the government committing them. 8 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 498)
  (House of Representatives.) A bill to be offered as a substitute for the bill reported by the Committee on Military Affairs to consolidate companies, battalions, regiments and brigades. Richmond, 1865. 3 p. 24 1/2 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 499)
  Amendment to section 3rd of the bill to be entitled An act to authorize the consolidation of companies, battalions and regiments. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 500)
  A bill to increase the efficiency of the cavalry of the Confederate States. 4 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 501)
  (House bill no. 319.) A bill more effectually to prevent and punish absenteeism and desertion in the army. 2 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 505)
  (House of Representatives no. 288.) A bill to be entitled An act authorizing the promotion of officers, non-commissioned officers and privates, for distinguished valor and skill or for peculiar competency and general merit. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 506)
  (House of Representatives, no. 322.) A bill to be entitled An act repealing certain abatements from the property tax and income tax, and amending the said tax laws. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 507)
  (House of Representatives, no. 323.) A bill to be entitled An act to provide payment for horses killed or lost in the service of the Confederate States. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 509)
  An act to provide for the more efficient execution of conscription, and for the arrest of deserters and absentees from the armies. 4 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 511)
  (House bill no. 326.) A bill to be entitled An act to make appropriations for the support of the government of the Confederate States of America, from the first day of January to the thirtieth day of June eighteen hundred and sixty-five. 12 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 512)
  Joint resolution of confidence in the thanks to President Jefferson Davis [by the Senate and House of Representatives of the State of Florida. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 513)
  Resolution [in relation to peace and independence. Richmond, 1865.] 1 p. 24 1A cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 515)
  (House of Representatives, no. 183.) A bill to be entitled An act to consolidate the public debt. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 516)
  (House of Representatives, no. 184.) A bill to be entitled An act to provide means to carry on the war. 3 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 517)
  (House of Representatives, no. 337. -Secret.) A bill to be entitled An act to levy additional taxes for the year 1865, for the support of the government. 4 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 518)
  Resolutions of the State of Texas, concerning peace, reconstruction, and independence. 3 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 519)
  (House bill, no. 338.) A bill to be entitled An act to levy and collect taxes for the common defence, and for the support of the government for the year 1865, and to repeal certain tax laws. 8 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 520)
  (House of Representatives, no. 342.) A bill to be entitled An act providing for the auditing and payment of properly authenticated claims. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 521)
  (House of Representatives, no. 343.) A bill to be entitled An act providing for the auditing and payment of properly authenticated claims against the Cotton Bureau in the Trans-Mississippi Department. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 522)
  (House of Representatives, no. 344.) A bill to be entitled An act to provide for auditing and payment for horses and equipments taken from dismounted cavalrymen for the use of the government. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 523)
  (House of Representatives, no. 349.)A bill to amend An act to organize forces to serve during the war. 3 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 524)
  (Secret.)Resolution concerning additional taxes for the year 1865. 3 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 525)
  (House of Representatives, no. 282.) A bill to be entitled An act for the prevention of frauds on the revenues of the PostofFice Department, and prohibiting the transportation of mailable matter over the post routes of the Confederate States by unauthorized associations of persons. 6 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 527)
  (Secret.) (House of Representatives, no. 361.) A bill to provide for the establishment of a Bureau for Special and Secret Service. 8 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 528)
  (Secret.) (House of Representatives, no. 362) A bill to be entitled "An act to provide means to carry on the war." 7 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 529)
  Resolutions adopted by the officers and men of the 57th Virginia Regiment. 2 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 530)
  Resolutions passed at a meeting of the Ninth Virginia Infantry-January 25, 1865. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 531)
  Resolutions passed at a meeting of the 14th Virginia Infantry-January 24, 1865. 2 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 535)
  (House.)Resolutions adopted by Bratton's Brigade, South Carolina Volunteers, January 30th, 1865. 3 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 536)
  (House.) Resolutions adopted by Company "H", "I" and "K" Thirteenth Virginia Infantry, January 28, 1865. 2 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 537)
  (House.) Resolutions adopted by Humphrey's Mississippi Brigade, Army of Northern Virginia, February 3, 1865. 1 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 538)
  (House.) Resolutions adopted by McGowan's Brigade, South Carolina Volunteer. 1 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 540)
  (House of Representatives, no. 367.) A bill to be entitled An act to increase the military force of the Confederate States. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 541)
  Amendment to the negro soldier bill. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 542)
  (Secret Session.) (House bill no. 370.) A bill to amend An act to organize forces to serve during the war. 3 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 543)
  (House bill.) A bill making appropriations to supply a deficiency in the appropriation for the Department of Justice for the half year ending December 31st, 1864. 1 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 544)
  Resolutions adopted by a meeting of the people of Powhatan, held in the courthouse on February court day, 1865. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 545)
  (House of Representatives, no. 378.) A bill to provide for the immediate payment of arrears due to the army and navy. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 547)
  Joint resolutions expressing the sense of Congress on the subject of the late peace commission. 4 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 548)
  (House bill.) A bill to increase the efficiency of the cavalry of the Confederate States. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 550)
  (House of Representatives, no. 386.) A bill making further regulations for the taxation of banks and bank notes, and for the confiscation of such notes held by alien enemies. 6 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 551)
  (House bill no. 391.) A bill to provide means to pay the army and navy, and carry on the war. 4 p. 25 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 553)
  (House of Representatives, no. 341.)A bill requiring suit to be brought against persons connected with the Cotton Bureau and Cotton Office in Texas. 3 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 560)
  Amendment to the bill offered by Mr. J.M. Smith, to amend the act to organize forces to serve during the war. 4 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862-1865 (Box 2, Folder 562)
  Calendar of the House of Representatives. [Richmond, 1862-65.] v.p. DGW: April 15, 1862; January 11, 1864; January 25, 1864; January 9, 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 2, Folder 577)
  Majority report of the Committee on Foreign Affairs. 6 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 2, Folder 578)
  Minority report of the Committee on Foreign Affairs, presented by Mr. Smith, of Alabama. 1 p. 22 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 583)
  Report of Committee on Quartermaster and Commissary Departments on case of Major Frank G. Ruffin. 3 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 591)
  Minority report of the Committee of Ways and Means on the tax bill. 4 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 597)
  Mr. Roger's minority report. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 598)
  Report of the Special Committee on the charge of corruption made in the Richmond Examiner, January 7, 1864. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 2, Folder 599)
  (House of Representatives-Secret session.) Minority report on the currency. 4 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 600)
  Report of Special Committee on the pay and clothing of the Army. 5 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 601)
  Report of the Special Committee, on the Payment of Claims. 7 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1861 (Box 3, Folder 612)
  President's message. 8 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1861
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 3, Folder 617)
  [Message to the President of the Congress, transmitting communications from all the departments, except the War Department.18 p. 21 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 3, Folder 618)
  Message of the President. 4 p. 21 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 3, Folder 621)
  President's message and accompanying documents. 74 3 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 623)
  Message of the President. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 624)
  Message of the President [transmitting a copy of an act of the Legislature of South Carolina, offering a guaranty by that state of the bonds of the Confederate States.2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 626)
  Message of the President. 1 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 627)
  President's message. 29 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 628)
  Veto message. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 629)
  President's message. 5 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 631)
  President's message. 7 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 632)
  Message of the President. 5 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 633)
  Message of the President. 13 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 635)
  Message of the President, [transmitting a communication from Hon. Howell Cobb, former President of the Provisional Congress, relative to the preparation of copies of the journals of that body, and proceedings of the Convention.4 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 637)
  Message of the President, [submitting the report of the commissioners to confer with the President of the United States with a view to the restoration of peace.4 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 697)
  Resolutions of Forsberg's Brigade, Wharton's Division, n.p.1865. 2 p. 24 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 816)
  Report of the Superintendent of Public Printing April 26, 1864. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 3, Folder 824)
  Attorney General's report February 26th, 1862. 7 p. 21 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 827)
  Communication from Attorney General Dec. 15, 1863, [submitting additional estimates for the expenditures of the Department of Justice.4 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863